Hey, what are you doing?
おい、何してるの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Sorry.
すいません
What are you sorry for?
何がすいませんの?
what?
なに?
Did you find someone you were interested in, so you invited him there?
気の人さん見つけたから誘導したの?
Hey, run away, you can have it.
なあ、逃げろ持てるもん
Come on for now.
とりあえずおいで
Shall we go home?
家行こうか
I really don't like home either.
本当に家も嫌です
Let's go to the apartment.
マンション行こう
Hey, come on.
ほら、おいで
I really hate my house too.
家も本当に嫌です
Because I don't have a house.
家とかないから
Come here.
こっち来い
Come on, come on, come on.
おいで、おいで、おいで
I really don't like home either.
本当に家も嫌です
yeah?
ん?
what?
なに?
please.
お願いします
Please stop.
やめてください
Mom, what are you doing?
お母さん、何してるの?
Are you loud?
大声ですか?
Hey, what are you doing?
なあ、どうすんの?
Sorry.
すいません
For now, come over there.
とりあえずあちへ来い
Come on, come on.
おいで、おいで
What room?
何号室?
I really hate home.
家は本当に嫌です
I know, but.
分かってるけど
What did you shoot?
なにしょったん?
Sorry.
すいません
What did you shoot?
なにしょったん?
Sorry, I'm sorry.
すいません、ちゃんめんな
What should I do?
どうすんの?
It's no good at home.
家はダメだよ
Are you going to give it back?
返すの?
Hey.
なあ
Are you getting your money back?
お金、金返してる?
Are you going to give it back?
返すの?
I guess I'll take a break until now.
これまで休憩しちゃうよな
What should I do?
どうすんの?
Sorry.
すいません
What are you sorry for?
なにがすいません?
Are you talking about work?
お仕事言ってるの?
No.
ないです
Are you loud?
大声ですか?
Shall I scream?
叫ぼうか?
I don't like it.
嫌です
I have a boyfriend.
彼氏がいるよ
No, mom.
いや、お母さん
Mom, please call me.
お母さん、電話してください
Call me.
電話して
Sorry.
すいません
I'll come to the office, so mom can choose right away.
事務所来るから、お母さんがすぐ選べ
I hate that sentence.
一文嫌です
Well, let's go.
じゃあ、行こうか
Come to the office.
事務所来い
Yes, sorry.
はい、すいません
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
I'll run away.
逃げちゃう
What should I do?
どうすんの?
どうしようか
Why did you run away?
なんで逃げたの?
It was scary.
怖かったです
Was it scary?
怖かった?
I was scared if I didn't use contact too.
こっちも連絡使わないと怖かったわ
Let's get in touch.
連絡はしようよ
Did the police say that?
警察でそうで言った?
I didn't say that.
言ってないです
That's what I'm saying.
言ってるよな
Why do you say what you say?
なんで言うことするの?
I'll tell you separately at home.
家で別に言ってもらう
Even if I get ripped off, all my subordinates are different,
俺がパクられても、違う部下が全員、
Because he will properly avenge you.
ちゃんと仇を打ってくれるから
What should I do?
どうする?
Sorry.
すいません
Take a picture of the face of the mother you set,
設定したお母さんの顔写真を撮って、
Shall we all fight?
みんなで戦おうか
There's no problem if you leave me alone.
放ってくれでは問題ないんだけどね
What should I do, Reina-san?
どうしようか、麗奈さん
What should I do?
どう したらいいですか?
どうしようか
What should I do?
どうしようかね
What do you think I should do?
どうしたらいいと思うかね
You can't even think about that when you're 19 years old?
19歳だとそんなこと考えられんか?
What should I do?
どうしたらいいか
I don't understand?
わからん?
Don't you understand?
わからんの?
Mom read it, mom put it in.
お母さん読んで、お母さん入れて、
Parents and children should take responsibility, Reina-chan,
親子供するか、 麗奈ちゃんがちゃんと責任取って、
Because you'll get it back with a sex video.
ハメ撮りで返してくれるから
I don't like either.
どっちも嫌です
Do you dislike both?
どっちも嫌?
Understood.
わかった
I'm going to send the video I took the other day to my mom.
この前撮った動画、お母さんに送るわ
No.
ダメです
Let's send it as a GIGA file.
GIGAファイルにして送っておこう
By short message.
ショートメッセージで
Please stop.
やめてください
I don't like it.
嫌だね
So what should I do?
じゃあどうしようか
If you're going to do it, have fun doing it.
やるのやったら楽しくやろうね
Nico, why don't you smile?
ニコって笑ってみ?
I have to choose one or the other.
どっちかにしないとね
Contact your mom or related today.
お母さんに連絡するか、 今日は関連して
Is that okay?
それでいい?
I hope you understand.
お聞き分けがいいじゃんか
Why are you running away?
なんで逃げるんだよ
She has a cute body after all.
せっかくかわいしい体してるのにな
How many cups did you use?
何カップやったっけ?
Did you have an F cup?
Fカップやったっけ?
yes.
はい
Are you still with your boyfriend?
彼氏とまだ続いてるの?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
Oh, you don't need it?
あ、いらんの?
how was it?
どう だった?
Divided?
分かれた?
Which one?
どっちなの?
I'm here.
います
What?
なんの?
Should I contact my boyfriend?
彼氏に連絡しようか?
Should I send the video to my boyfriend?
彼氏に動画送ろうか?
Please stop.
やめてください
It's big.
で っかいね
Let's have fun today.
今日はじっくり楽しくやろうよ
Shall we give ourselves plenty of time?
時間をたっぷりやろうか
Are you coming today?
今日は来る?
Weren't you meeting your boyfriend?
彼氏と会ってたんじゃないの?
It's Batsugo In Style.
バツゴムインスタイルだね
amazing.
すごい
It's Batsugo In Style.
バツゴムインスタイルだね
Is your mother a Kyoryu too?
お母さんもキョウリュウなの?
yes.
はい
How many cups are there?
何カップある?
Mom is also an F cup.
お母さんもFカップです
Is your mother also an F cup?
お母さんもFカップ?
That's amazing.
すごいな
Shall I call your mother?
お母さん呼ぼうか
Let's call your mom.
お母さん呼ぼうよ
I'll do it with my mom.
俺、お母さんとやるわ
Look at your mom being fucked next to you.
横でお母さんがやられてるの見てや
I want to heal this area soon.
このうちにここをやさしたいから
No.
ダメです
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
yes.
はい
So come back and let us stay here?
じゃあ帰りに来て、俺たちはここに居てくれるか?
It's a style bullet.
スタイルバツゴムだね
Are you still going to have sex?
まだわけでエッチでもするのか?
Would you like everyone to see it?
みんなに見てもらおうか
I don't like it.
嫌ね
Remember it.
覚え出して
You've been through a lot of trouble, so make sure to smile.
せっかくやられて、ちゃんと笑ってよ
Smile.
ニコニコして
It's a style bullet rubber.
スタイルバツゴムですよ
Just put your foot down.
足置いてほら
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいんかな?
My boobs look lonely.
おっぱいは寂しそうだな
The rubber band is also a style.
バツゴムもスタイルだね
Kuri-chan is twitching.
クリちゃん、ヒクヒクしてるよ
Would you like a convenient snack for mom?
お母さんの便利おつまみする?
I want you to come at least once.
一回に来てほしいわよ
Rare man, tell me.
レアマン、教えて
I wish it was found out here.
ここでばれてたらいいんやな
I haven't gotten my money back either.
お金も返してないし
What should I do?
どうする?
Is it water consumption?
水の消費やろ?
It's a rubber band.
バツゴムだね
Your breasts have gotten a little bigger, haven't they?
ちょっとおっぱい大きくなったんじゃん?
Isn't it about a J cup?
Jカップくらいになってない?
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's a style bulletin board.
スタイルバツゴムだよ
Let's move the top hair back.
上の毛を後ろにしてみよう
Where do you feel it?
どこが感じるのかな?
Let's go look for it.
探していこうかね
Were your breasts rubbed from behind?
後ろからおっぱい揉まれた?
Let's do our best today.
めちっこくやろうか、今日は
How much can I pay today?
今日中にいくら払えるのか?
How much can I pay back by tomorrow?
明日中にいくら返せるのか?
I have to tell you.
教えてもらわないとな
Yes, answer me.
はい、答えて
Leave this behind.
この 後ろ置いて
how much?
いくら?
It won't be possible until tomorrow.
明日までは無理です
Is it impossible?
無理なの?
When can I do it?
いつやっていけるの?
It's half a year later.
半年後です
No way, no way.
無理無理
I wonder how many times I have to take it for half a year.
半年だったら何回取らなさめだかね
半年後?
So I'll take this today and upload it tomorrow.
じゃあこれを今日撮ったやつ、明日アップロードするわ
Just keep in mind that it's on various video sites.
色んな動画サイトに載ってると思っておけよ
It will already be everyone's side dish the day after tomorrow.
もう 明後日にはみんなのおかずになってるわな
Your father won't see it.
お父さんに見られんじゃん
What would you do if your daughter came out when you were looking for the father?
お父さん何でしころかなって探した時に娘が出てきたらどうすん
of?
の?
I wondered why Reina was in it.
なん でれいなが出てるんだよってなるで
Would you like me to work on a cruise ship?
計列船で働いてもらおうか
Tell me anything else.
あとどれも申して
why?
なんで?
Do you dislike it?
嫌な?
Should I do 3 or 4 peas?
3ピーか4ピーしようか
Well, I can't be happy anymore, so mommy let me hold you.
じゃあもうれいないらんから、お母さん抱かしてくれて
Do you dislike it?
嫌な?
What feels good around here?
この辺どこ気持ちいいの?
Which part is easier to feel?
どの辺が感じやすい?
It's the whole body.
全身ですね
My whole body feels good
全身気持ちいいん
mosquito?
か?
Guri-chan is standing.
グ リちゃん立ってるよ
That's a great style.
すごいスタイルだね
You look kind of happy.
なんか嬉しそうな顔してるね
Did you say it quietly?
静かに言っちゃった?
You can speak louder.
もっと声出していいぞ
Don't worry.
気にせず
Are you the owner?
オーナーにしてんの?
Want to try it yourself?
自分でしてみる?
You want me to do that, right?
してほしいんだろ?
Tell me what you want.
どうしてほしいか言ってみろ
It's cute.
かわいいね
Those are beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱいだね
Are you feeling well?
気 持 ちいいの?
It has great style.
スタイル抜群ですよ
Spread my legs.
俺の足広げろ
Can I go?
行っちゃっていいですか?
Please go.
行っちゃってください
What are you doing?
何されてるの?
I was being licked.
舐められてました
Why are you being licked?
何舐められて
Do you want to do it?
る の?
I'll send a message to your mother.
お母さんに向けてメッセージ送ってやるから
Don't close your legs.
足閉じるな
What's wrong?
何が駄目なの?
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
That's terrible.
やばいね
Let's set it up properly.
ちゃんと仕掛いてほら
It's not showing properly.
ちゃんと映ってないよ
That's it.
それだ
No, no, no.
ダメダメダメ
It's getting bigger.
くり大きくなってるな
It's amazing.
すごいですよ
It's really tight even with your fingers.
指でもすごい締まりですよ
I want to show you my mother.
お母さんの見せてあげたいね
Because I've become a good woman.
いい女になったよって
She's a good woman.
いい女ですよ
Would you like your father to see it?
お父さんで見てもらう?
Are you going to go again while saying that?
そんな言いながらまた行くんやろ?
Even though your father is talking about it, you're leaving again, aren't you?
お父さんの話してるのにまた行っちゃうんやろ?
Very tight
すごい締まり
is.
です
Dad, this is going to make me cry.
お 父さん泣いちゃうよこれ
You must be putting a lot of pressure into your fingers.
指 に力入ってるじゃんね
It feels good.
気持ちいいな
It's not useless.
駄目じゃないよ
Wrap your fingers together.
指巻いてほら
Be quiet.
静かにして
Got it?
分かった?
reply.
返事
Here, roll it up tightly.
ほら、しっかり巻いてほら
It won't come off.
抜けないですよ
A lot more have come, haven't they?
まだいっぱい来たやろ?
I'll call you.
電話してやるわ
Call me from inside, not using your own name,
自分のネームじゃなくて、 内側から電話して、
You're asking me to lick you more, right?
もっと舐めてくださいって言うやろ?
Come on, hurry up.
ほら、早く
Please lick it more.
も っと舐めてください
Okay.
よっしゃ
How much force should I apply?
どんぐらいの力にする?
It's amazing.
すごいですよ
How much force should I apply?
どんぐらいの力にする?
How much force should I use?
ど んぐらいの力にする?
How much force should I apply?
どんぐらいの力にする?
Shall we loosen up a little more?
もうちょっと緩めようか?
Be gentle at first.
最初は優しく
It probably feels better this way.
多分こっちの方が気持ちいいですよ
This feels good too.
これも気持ちいいな
I'll stop after I've done it 30 times.
30回行ったらやめてやるわ
Go 30 times.
30回行け
Place your belly 30 times, 30 times once.
30回腹を置く30回1回
I would like the rest to be placed here as well.
残りのやつはここにも置いてほしいよ
That's impossible.
無理ですね
I'm standing.
立ってますよ
Call me from inside.
内側から電話して
It won't stop.
ストップしないよ
What stops?
何がストップ?
This is your perverted stop.
こっちはお前のヘンサイストップしちゃってるんだよ
What stops?
何がストップ?
I'm playing Spokky for the country.
国取りスポッキーしてますよ
Do you want a safe?
金庫欲しい?
Want to put it in a safe?
金庫入れたい?
I can't go in yet.
まだ入れないよ
Please call me.
電話してください
terrible.
やばい
I was there earlier.
さっきとこっちは行ってました
now?
今?
It's amazing.
すごいですよ
Shall I put it in?
入れようか
Let's put it in.
入れよう
What should I do?
どうする?
terrible.
やばい
Is this the best?
これが一番いいのかな?
It doesn't come in at first.
最初は入らない
I had a hard time getting into it at first.
最初なかなか入らなかったのに
I'll put it in right now.
今すーっと入れますよ
I have a lot of things to bring.
いっぱいの持ち物あるよ
use?
使う?
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいあるよ
It's like a hedge bar.
ヘッジバーみたいなのあるよ
Doesn't this feel good?
これ気持ちいいんじゃない?
copper?
どう?
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
Is this dangerous?
これやばい?
copper?
どう?
Doesn't it feel good already?
もう気持ちいいんじゃない?
Okay.
いいよ
Fill it up.
い っぱい入って
what?
何?
I won't say it.
言わない
I don't know.
分かんないよ
Say it properly.
ちゃんと言って
There are still many others.
まだ他にもいっぱいあるね
Which one do you guess?
どれ当てる?
Want to hit it more comfortably?
もっと気持ちよく当てる?
It's a woman's ball.
女ボールだよ
What should I do?
どうする?
Are you interested?
興味ある?
Insert this, and it will hit first.
これ、 挿入して、 先、 当たるよ、
this.
これ
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
Let's put it in slowly.
ゆっくり入れてみよう
Should I stop if it hurts?
痛かったらやめようか
copper?
どう?
Shall we go in?
入り出そう?
Hey, this is it, President.
ちょっとこれは、社長
This is tough.
これは厳しいね
After all, hedge bars feel better.
やっぱりヘッジバーの方が気持ちいい
What kind of power is good?
威力はどんなものがいい?
Which is better, weak or like this?
弱めか、 この感じか、どっちがいい?
Weak.
弱め
Weak?
弱め?
this?
これ?
Which one?
どっち?
This way?
こっち?
Which one?
どっち?
this?
これ?
You're setting up a photo.
写真を仕掛けてるじゃん
Shall I guess again?
もう 一回当てようか
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
This way?
こっち?
Which?
ど っち?
Would a toy be better?
おもちゃの方がいいのかな?
Is this better than licking?
舐めるより、 舐めるより、 こっちかな?
Should I just keep guessing?
当てっぱなしでしようか
It's so fluffy.
ふちゃふちゃじゃん
Was it ever finished?
仕上がりだことあったっけ?
Have you ever done that?
したことある?
do not have?
ない?
What kind of weakness is licking?
舐めってどういう弱めなの?
Does that mean it's dangerous?
やばいってこと?
I'll do something like that.
そんなことやるで
It's beautiful.
綺麗っすよ
My butt is also responding.
お尻も反応してますよ
Have you ever had your butt done?
お尻やったことあんの?
Hey?
なあ?
Is it common?
よくあるの?
Do you really want to fuck my butt?
まさかお尻やりたいの?
I really don't like it.
さすがに嫌やろ
Next time, after the test, I'll give you a butt.
じゃあ次、検査を終えたら お尻しようか
I have no interest in it as it is.
このままある興味ないから
I'm going to do my ass here soon.
そ ろそろお尻ここやるから
Shall I take your butt too?
お尻もいっちゃう?
No butt?
お尻はダメ?
What is this?
なにこれ?
No butt?
お尻はダメ?
I'll do my butt here.
お尻ここやるから
I guess I can do it then.
じゃあしてもらおうかな
Shall I do it for you?
やってもらおうか
Isn't it delicious?
うまいじゃんか
It was popular in stores as well.
店でも人気よかったんすよ
That's right.
ですよね
It was completely unexpected, and it started to hit me.
ちゃんと予想外で ケツつきだしたね
You're good at it.
上手っすよ
It would be nice to have a cute Sibella too.
かわいいシベラも持っていいじゃん
You look professional.
プロなみっすよ
If you get used to giving blowjobs, I'll lower the test by 10,000 yen.
もしフェラで活かされたら 検査1万円下げてやるわ
Seriously lick it.
真剣に舐めろ
You're licking me, kid.
舐めてるね、この子
teeth.
は
Are you a student?
学 生っすか?
I'm a young college student.
少子大生っすわ
It feels good.
気持ちいいわ
Lick it properly, here.
ちゃんと舐めろ、ほら
I guess you're trying to be nice.
いいかとしてるんじゃん
That's outstanding, boss.
抜群ですよ、社長
Just kidding.
冗談です
Your breasts look nice too.
おっぱいもいい感じやろ
Oh yeah, do you want to enter?
そうそう、入れたい?
Yeah.
うん
I want to join, boss.
僕 が入れたいっすよ、社長
Please put it in.
入れたってください
That's good, Reina-chan.
うまいね、麗奈ちゃん
Now, what should we do?
さあ、どうしようか
It's a great constraint.
すごい縛りです
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's outstanding.
抜群ですよ
Now, which body should I choose next?
さあ、次はどの体にしようかな
Do you still want it to be firm?
まだパンパンついてほしいか?
Yeah.
うん
I'm concerned about this, Mr. President.
これ が気になりますよ、社長
This is it.
これですよ
This is what's pulling me in.
これが引っ込んでるんですね
Shall we stand for a moment?
ちょっと立たしましょうか
I'm coming.
いきますよ
Now, which body should I choose next?
さあ、次はどの体にしようかな
what
何を
Do you want to?
した いの?
Back.
バ ック
Well then, let's do it in the back.
じゃあ、バックでしようか
Come on, tease me.
ほら、いじついてよ
It's a great constraint.
すごい縛りです
It's still to come.
まだこれからだよ
You can put it in with Lemptu.
レンプツで入れるでしょ
That's right.
ですね
Just do it first.
そのまま最初にしてください
That's right.
ですね
It seems like I was immediately taken aback by how good the restraints were.
何の縛りよさにすぐいっちゃったみたいな
I left right away.
すぐいっちゃったよ
Another one
もう一
Turn it in.
回 入れてやれ
I went there again, so I'm sure I'll put a bang on it.
もう一回いったからバンバンつけるでしょ
It's a great constraint.
すごい縛りです
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
I'm starting to feel good too, so I'll let you in later.
俺も気持ちよくなってきたから後で入れさせてや
good?
いい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Well, let's include me too.
じゃあ、俺も入れよう
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気持ちいいのか?
Come on, let's go upstairs.
さあ、上行ってもらおう
mosquito.
か
You look so happy.
う れしそうじゃん
You can go.
行っていいよ
Yes, let's go.
はい、行こう
What happened?
どうしたよ
I went quietly.
静かに行っちゃった
I tried harder.
もっと頑張ったよ
Let's do it.
やらんとろ
Mom will be angry.
お母さん怒るよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Ah, that.
あ、それ
Yes, I'll go.
はい、行く
Okay.
いいよ
I'm going too.
俺も行っちゃうよ
Peace, peace.
ピースしろ、ピースしろ
Tell me you were let inside.
中に出されましたって言ってね
It was served inside.
中に出されました
It's an agreement.
合意ですって
They agreed to let me in.
合 意で中に出しましたって
By agreement, I was let out.
合 意で中に出されました
He says he will bring the money tomorrow.
お金は明日持ってきますって言う
I'll bring the money tomorrow.
お金は明日持ってきます
200,000 tomorrow.
明日20万
I'll bring 200,000 tomorrow.
明日20万持ってきます
You know what will happen if you don't bring 200,000.
20万持ってこなかったらどうなるか分かるよな
Got it?
分かった?
Then I'll go home.
じゃあ俺帰るから
Do it properly.
ちゃんとしろよ
I'm tired.
お疲れです
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ
Come tomorrow.
明日来いよ
Please do it again tomorrow.
明日もまたお願いね
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です